I saw how much chili you put in everything from
seafood to seafood.
Very fond of.  You don't have hemorrhoids.
Nothing.  Let's see the butts.
[laughter]
So you didn't do anything.  Where are you?
Mommy.  Oh, I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.  Oh, I'm sorry,
mommy. You're going to have to go.  [laughter]
Then he told her not to
go out at night.  Because the road
we were on was
dark because there were no lights.   The baby
will be born.  There is a problem.
You laughed, mommy, but her face seemed to
get angry.
You must have
really had a crush on Bimbi before.  Delicious.
I'm eating.  Do you have crust?  This is
what mommy crang avoids
[music]
hello team r.  [laughter]
Hello netizens.  For today's video,
I'm excited because you know when I was
pregnant, especially [music] during
my first trimester, it was one of the things
I watched and it was one of the reasons
why I had cravings and suddenly
I was able to cook something.
Just like a rotten chicken.  I
only found out about the
chicken I got from him and it was so delicious
.  So I'm excited that
he'll cook for me because of course we're going to have a
baby soon.  I'm about to get
my watermelon out.  That's why
team Ra
Mommy Ra is with us today.
Hello.  Team R. Ma'am, you are the mommy
here.
Okay.  [laughter] What, ma'am?  Maybe
the stomach is fat.  Mommy is shy but
she doesn't seem shy.  What is
he like, right?  Hello,
you are vlogging in the middle of Hong Kong.  You are ashamed.
Why are you holding on?  We can [laugh]
.
Just nervous.  Nervous.
Mommy's name is Mommy Riza.
Then Riza is Riza.  How many
children do you have?  [music]
Yes.
Why did you join this?
[laughter]
That's talent.  Talented.  What is
yours?  What will you give to
our talent today?  The only talent,
ma'am, is cooking.  That's really all
you did there.  Did he do something
?  That's hilarious.  Oh okay,
look at
you, mommy, it looks like you're just having a heart attack
[laughter]
Champ, what he did was wrong,
I'll tell you, I'm sorry.
Oh, that's the last one.  Last 1 2 3 go you're
penty
ma pint of him.  Hello!  Before we continue the
video, I just have something to say to
you, especially to our
fellow OFWs abroad.  Who else
are our partners and those
we trust when we
give love to our
countrymen when it comes to our padala
or pad love?  Of course, there is nothing else but
the top send, especially to those
from Australia, the US, Canada, Europe, the UK, the
UAE, and now there is one in Bahrain as well.
Because of the top cent, mobile
banking fees and those on your e-wallets are zero.
Your loved ones will receive Padle Love quickly
because the exchange rates are competitive.
So if you know an OFW or you are an
OFW, don't wait any longer.
Download and share
Taptop Send immediately.  And don't
forget to use my code for
your first transaction to get
an extra $20.  Use my code Alex G.
So if you are an OFW, don't
think about it anymore.  Download, Tap,
send.  And then back to the video.
Ah, what are we going to eat, king crab?
Yes, king crab because I saw what
you were doing, seafood.  That's why
you said your seafood was a bit raw, right?  So
of course I can't go to the raw yet.
I saw.  You are good at making
sauce.  Mommy.  Oh, mommy and I still have a glass
.
Strength glass.  You're strong.
[music]
Okay, ma'am, then we'll go ahead and look for it.
[laughter]
Shy.  It's him.  Why aren't
you shy?  Mommy is shy.  Yes.  Miss
Tony because you are Tony.  Oh, sorry, sorry,
Miss Alex.  You know I'm itching for
what I have here, my cubicle here.  I don't know why I suddenly felt so itchy
.  Why are you still
Tony of Tony?   Of course
not, Miss Tony, because
Ah, okay.  You're wrong.  Don't treat
me like you can't take it back. So
why didn't you become shy?  Who
among you is not [music] shy?  It seems like it's just
me.  So it's just you, no one said no,
but what if he was just embarrassed
now because he's Miss Alex B. Yes.  But
hey, it's like you really
[laughter]
like you really want to kiss me
because I've only been watching you and
now you're here in front of me.  Wow!
I watched you too.  What is
your favorite food now that you are pregnant?  Oh, sorry,
you know, it's different, but it's just a matter of what
your cravings are.
But don't text.
Then, mom, let's start.  So what
we're going to do now is make the seafood sauce
.  Okay.  What is the sauce for
our seafood?  Okay, sir.  We have butter,
garlic, garlic powder, and this
cay pepper.  It's really my first time, ma'am,
because it's just me.   This is
your first time collaborating.
Just the second one.  Yes.  Who is your first?
Sir idol.  Good morning.  Good morning
idols.  This is a funny idol.
I saw it last week.  I saw.  I saw it,
I'll delete it
for you.   Just
for me.  You can sit down because
I'm not very big. Yes, and it seems like
mommy and I are just sitting there
[laughter] Yes, of course, ma'am, because of course
this is a special occasion because I'm cooking for the team, ma'am, thanks
for inviting me.  So I hope
you like the
sauce, I hope we can cook it because it's been a
while [laughter] I hope this is
butter first.  [music] Butter first, I hope
you like it.  But you can't have
spicy food, ma'am.   It's
okay.  Just don't overdo it
.  But don't.  It's okay.  Why are
you putting that?  [music] Well,
we all love
spicy food.  Wow.  I saw a lot of
you putting chili in whatever
seafood you like.
You don't have hemorrhoids, there's no pity
in looking at the butts,
[laughter]
pet reveal.  You seem to be attracted to
spicy food.  Let me see
your butts.  Okay, I'll put some
garlic in it, ma'am.  [music]
But Raiza mommy boasted like, "
Oh, no, ma'am, I'm so excited,
I'm not."  I always
remind her, ma'am, that you should always be
kind and never change.  You're the way
you used to be, so why do
you look at me so negatively? It's like you're
trying to change
.  Did I make your life miserable for you?
[laughter] I think it's different from
others if someone is sometimes a bread winner or
helpful, right?  It seems like sometimes you
speak too highly.  Yes.  This is it.
So how did you do it?  You're great,
mommy, because when they were just kids,
I always taught them how to
be better than their siblings, not like
I'm the one who's
acting like this.  Not him.  I might get kicked out
of the house if I do that.
I've never heard him say, "What is this
music?" or "What is this?"   Okay, that's up to
you, you take care of
that.  That's how wonderful it was to raise
you.  Yes.  It's not really natural
[laughter] it's not good to be not so
you didn't do anything, where are you?  Mommy, I'm
sorry, mommy, you've already done CR.
[laughter]
So many people notice him
like that.  He's not ashamed of that.
He [music] is not shy.
One of his playmates said, "Don't
go out at night. It's scary when I
meet you. You're so tiny.
You look like a child when you
say you're just a child because you're only that age
. When you're like that, you're a
child. Who doesn't you
really look at? [laughter]
You don't know it, it's like I'm trying to fight
you. Of course I hurt you.
So you told mommy. Mm.
What did you say?
I said it's okay, son. It's nothing
. It's just a joke. Because
ma'am, he's so small,
he's so small. This kid is also a bit dark
.
Mommy's smallness makes him look like he's become a grandfather
or he's just that small
. Are you that small, ma'am? So that's all
he's really small. That's it. Who called you which
little one? It's big, big, because he's
small, then the one that looks like [music] mature, mature,
think. But  Mommy, do
n't you feel hurt when you're told
that?
Of course, that hurts a mother.
But I don't
pay attention to them. I just let it go because there's
nothing we can do if
I say that. So you're not going to fight? Oh
no. Then I told her not to
go out at night. Because it's
our road, the one we saw like this,
the road is dark because there's no lights.
You're going to get hit by a car.
You're laughing, Mommy, she said she
might get hurt. So I told her to
always remember that it's better to be the one
being bullied than the one being bullied.
[Applause] What's that?
I cried when
you said that, I just heard that
[laughter] That's
right, that's in the Bible,
and the bullies are being picked up, you
can take it easy,
I said, okay, okay,
maybe just hold my hand, because they ordered me to be a mother,
I'm just sitting here because of course I'm
pregnant. Yes, boss, you're not allowed to move
[music],
Mommy. Go home. Okay  that ca
n't be eaten.
Go mommy one two go first. It's
really you. You go first. You were just a while ago,
what are you madam, you're getting angry,
you're feeling scolded
. Okay. Okay. 5 6 7 8
You should be quiet.
Yes. Then the king CR comes out
. [laughter]
[music]
Oh yeah.
I'm excited. Are you excited, mommy? Are
you nervous? Why are you still nervous
? He said we'll be together. Or
with tang. [laughter]
Hello team rangtana.
This is our king crab dish.
My God [music] this is the first time
Raiza and I will taste it. Just now
. Thank you very much for
inviting us and also for preparing
this King Cram for us. Actually
mommy, I really want king cram. That's
my craving right now. Since
I'm pregnant, you'll have the hot one.
[laughter] That's it
. That's why.
We'll use T's not in  That's all ours,
mommy. What do you call that
sauce, mommy?
What? Butter garlic. So
now let's start, mommy, with the
fat on his tentacles.
His tentacles are fat, right? Oh, what are we doing
here? Okay, let's meet at the
[laughter] party
.
Thank you, ma'am. Is it
me or not? Okay, I'm
here. Is it just you today, so it's like we're just going to have a little
fun, oh, do
you want this? Okay.
Yes, mommy is really kind. I hope
you'll do it for me too. Oh, okay, okay, thank you.
That's how delicious mommy's was. The meat was
really good.
That's fresh.
Delicious, delicious,
delicious. Let's talk. Let's see later
. Mommy prayed. Thank
you Lord Jesus. We were able to pray. I
prayed. Okay, I'm
going to hell. It's like [laughter] it's like
you're the only one who's like how are you,
like you don't even care about me,
you didn't take me to heaven. Okay,
thank you, okay.  What did you say
earlier, miss? [music] Team Ra, I was watching
earlier. I mean, let's eat
. Let's eat. I'm watching. Yes. It's
good. Mommy's eating.
Actually, sometimes you're like what. It
seems like we're not being carried anymore.
Hey, there you are. What time did you
arrive? How many years have you been in showbiz?
[music] 14. 14? Or in your 14 years,
you never thought about quitting. No,
I said that in the
interview, it was really my dream. Maybe
you're tired. No.
You never thought about it. It was really
your dream. Yes. [music] Mommy never
told you that we're a child.
Ah, she's not really supportive.
But what kind of decision did I make, it's not
like what happened to you
in [music] you joked about Tony Talk, isn't that the one
you
first ran to your mom? Yes. What
did mom say? Because she was the only one who
found out in the interview, hm, there was
no briefing.  that
something like that is really happening. How did
you know? [music]
That was in Tito Sen's interview.
Ah but when it was happening you didn't have any
idea.
What's the matter, you only let
me in once a week twice, it
seems obvious but there's no real
confirmation [music] that you're not
hurt, I'm the only
one in the dressing room. Mm. Then
they all got involved. I was only in one segment [music] and
then once a week. Are
you saying mommy like that?
Mm. But what's the point of her just being a bit of a
wimp? What were
you doing, ma'am, at that time, did
you feel discouraged?
Yes. What, ma'am, we cried, ma'am,
because we both cried when
we got home. It was my birthday [music] anyway
. I said let's just pray, I
said that.
Raya's sadness is really bad.
She's really crying all the time. I said, "Nak,
just pray." I said that. This is
just a test. I said, "Get over it  "
We'll do this too." [music] I said, "There are so
many other people, they're going through even more difficult
trials in
their lives.  That's how we are.  It's good that we have something
to eat.  Those kinds of things.  I'm sorry.
Please, I need some rice.
Yes, indeed.  [laughter]
But in your time on the show, haven't you ever made anyone
angry?  Enemy?  Nothing.  You're great
.  Because that's not
my circle.  TVJ.  Fight
[clears throat] TVJ.  They
really are family.  Wave [laughter]
at random.  So you were able to tape with
girls, what is this really about?  Bulaga
has it.  But I'm still young, so
I don't have any primitive skills yet.  Ah, you
really don't have anything like what
you want now, let's do something, let's see
who mommy's side is with.
Oh thank you [clears throat]
mommy you're missing out you're missing out you
skipped me this is it me
thank you mommy.  Oh, I did it,
I thanked you, but have you
ever been bashed, where did you cry, were
you affected, or were you even bashed?   Yes, there is
.  It seems like
the bash was unavoidable.
You're telling me to mommy I read the
comments or what are you going to do mommy if
that's what I said just let it go don't
hit me oh really yes that's it
but you're hurt mommy yes
I'm hurt but I'm just letting it go it's just like
ah it's like
Riza confronted you don't want to talk about it it's like
she's going to be sad it's like it's
over because people have their own
opinions because ma'am
that's what they want to say
just let them go that's what
I'm telling her don't hit them
don't be angry yes it's like
you never hit anything at home yes
but you get offended sometimes sometimes m
[music] what's the most you'll never
forget what's about you what's the comment about
me I used to be I can't forget a
comment on me Alex just told me
the fourem stone of gunsag
forgot but now it's like it's okay
you just accepted it
I accepted it when I was a kid it hurts
of course because that seems to mean doesn't it
seem like you're always comparing me to
my sister it's like the ending is
you're really the ugly one  That version
or are you the really cheap version? It
seems like
yours is ugly, but it's so beautiful.
[laughter] It was
you who commented.  It's no surprise
that the lady is so wet.
What is the most
unforgettable thing you will ever do?  I guess you forgot.
Because it's all about physical appearance.
Yes.  Like what's yours?  Yes.  This is
ugly.  These are so dark.  So
pretend you're the butt of the joke.
You're still offended.  Not anymore.  It's not
[music].  Get used to it.  You know why
you don't get offended because
your mom is there first, where do you get it?  Me too.
That's why I'm probably not too much of a
basher because
your family and support system are complete.  But
you haven't thought about it yet, maybe later
when I get a boyfriend.  Not yet
.  This is awesome.  Not
flirting yet.  [clears throat] Hey,
when you're 18, sometimes it feels like you're
just going to have a crush, just a crush.  Mm.
You're getting married.  So sometimes
you become conscious that you are no longer
what?  Not at all.  [music] Thank you.   Is
n't he yet?  Mommy, I have a crush.
I don't have any crushes or anything,
but I'm not the one who's no-conscious because
you're good at those things.  You know,
you don't seem to be flirting like I did
when I was a kid.  It feels like I'm getting so pretty that my
tongue is sticking out.  It's not like
that.   It's
not like that because when
I was a child, my mom always told me
how beautiful you are, my child.  You are prettier
than your sister.  Maybe it's
because my sister is a talented
noun.  So my sister,
you're even more beautiful when you sing.  You are more beautiful.
So when I was a kid, I felt like I was
actually prettier than my sister.  So when someone tells
me, "You're ugly, I'm not like that anymore."  So
it really matters what
you say to your child.  Son.  My point is that
I'm not too affected, because that's how
I grew up.  But if you
compare me to
your better sister, I'm a little upset
because you always tell me
I'm just pretty.  So my investment is just fine
.  This is the only thing that has kept
me going in this industry for so long, this
beautiful body.
Ah, his body is also a
mess.  He is a fool.  Yes.  And
later, I'll take you to the Viva Max
[laughter] taping.
Just kidding, mommy, this is
really fun to be with,
ma'am, right?   It's
me, ma'am.  I can't do it anymore.
Thank you.  That's why when I was a kid, I
felt like I was pretty, so my crush must have a
crush on me too because he kept telling
me I was pretty and
you were pretty.  What if
your crush rejects you?  Well, I always
get rejected because I'm not
very pretty.  It turns out that
my mother [laughs] lied, and that
my beauty was just a way to appease her.  It turns out it's not true, it
turns out I'm not beautiful either, so
I saw that, yes, it's really like
Bimbey used to be.
I'm eating delicious food.  Hey, do you know
Bimby?  I'm very close to that child.   What about that
kid?
Yes.  Are you the same age?  [laughter]
This isn't the story of Bimbi and I during the
private Benjamin days,
so we were always together, but
she was very happy with me.  He is a fool.
Sister Chris was surprised.  One time
he came to visit us at night and was surprised
why BB was hugging him so
close.  Then, sister Chris suddenly texted me
last night.
What?
What did you do to my son?  He's been
asking me where you're from?  What
show are you on on TV5?  He's always asking me.
So that's why Chris and I became friends
because of the baby, but we never
met again because when
you went to the states, we never did anything [music].  Nothing.  Last time
we met again was in 2025 [music].  We last
met in Japan in 2019.  How old are you?  14.
14 like that.  Ah, you're a young woman, and
Bim is 2 years younger [music]
than me.  Did you talk?
You guys bonded, right?  Just be quick.  It's
only now that we really
had the chance [music] to
bond again on Bulaga.  But when
you were kids, were you really close?
Really great.  Hi, what's up with the movie bossing?
I was so surprised by Bimby because
Bimby is also very down to earth.
It's like you don't know how to think
his mom is a
superstar.  That kid was really kind
.  I'm so happy that I'm still a
child.  He entered.  Are
you surprised?  I'm not surprised.  I haven't
seen him before.  You don't know.   It's
not my birthday because it's a surprise
to me that babe is the
last one.  So when we saw that, it was
really long
because of the height.
Yes.  We don't really have a bond.  So
when I saw him, I was happy too.
You really touched him, child.
This is really delicious.
Are you a crusader?
This is what mommy avoids, what kind of
crush [laughter]?  Yes, it looks like it's in college.  I have a
crush on him.  Do you have a crush?  [laughter]
They're really close
[music], they're so close to Dream that they're like
siblings.
There at the shooting.  So now
they met again.  Still the same.  It's funny what
you're doing.  But what about your crush now
?  It's not like [music] is just
friends.  Your crab is really delicious
.  You know what I'm going to do
[laughs] to break your neck.
That Bim is so tender.
Sobr is very tender. Until now,
his affection has been really super tender.
I still love you.   I
miss you.
Baby.  Very kind child.  I have a crush on him.
Yes.  I'm a mom.
[laughter]
Or did they even make me a pedophile?
Because you don't know just to
admit it.  [laughter]
And you, mommy, who is
your crush on TVJ [laughter]
if you had to choose.  Oh, that's it, okay?
Okay.  Oh
jojowain, it's going to be painful.  [laughter]
They're all my idols, ma'am.  jojowain
just or totropahin okay no no no
pretend joey de leon
ah totropahin
you totropahin why sir joey
totropahin
because what is kind and then what is
boss joy genius like that or eh
bossing
bossing also totropahin oh
because you are kind you are all kind no
totropahin you don't seem like what is
not
[laughter]
nothing like that ah
eh tito
totropahin also ah really friend zone
everyone gave you mommy but you didn't give
him back go ahead [laughter]
no okay mommy really loves
you thank you p did you and
mommy ever or this of course teenager did
you have a real fight no no
[music] eh he doesn't really fight he
really seems like you're acting
like you want to rebel no toos that's
him when you tell him that just keep
quiet
tears just fall
t's judi santos you're still [laughter] left just a
drop just a drop of tears ah that's just how
he is  Ma'am, he's not
fighting, he's not really, he's not the one,
let me stop the car, there's
nothing like that, there's nothing like
that, there's nothing, so you're
really scared of your mommy, in short, yes,
we're all scared,
but you're not the one who's so scared
that it's like you're not opening up to [music],
we're not the only ones,
I just call him dars,
aunt in Tagalog, [laughter]
dars, yes dars, but mommy, where are you in that
part of your life?  Oh well,
you didn't fight.  You are so proud
of your son.  When?  I started doing it
when Rai was still a child.
They're all not the
really naughty kids you always
[music] You always scold them
because if I just say one thing, they know
they're not going to be naughty anymore,
they're not going to be that naughty anymore.  That's why I'm so proud
of them because they're good kids
with their playmates and they don't
fight.  Yes, that's right.  What else do
you want Raya to do?  What is your dream
about Raya?  My dream is for
him to finish his studies.  That
he can still fulfill
his dreams.  Then what does he want?
Be a makeup artist or be a chef?  Mm
chef.  You're a chef, you can't cook, so
I don't care.  I said maybe
you can bake like that.
Cooking is also difficult, especially in
the heat, and he might not be able to
lift the big pan.  You know, it's
like mommy is trying to control you, like a
judge
when she went to Little Miss Philippines,
but cooking is like a
cow, you know, it's like
she's discouraging you [laughter]
'That's right, because your mommy is now
earning money too', is mommy proud?
Who told mommy to vlog?
First, that page was just a little
behind the scenes with me on Bulaga
or it started when I posted about
slippers or
that Halloween hall, and then it
seemed like we were enjoying him
cooking.  He showed me
how to cook my baon.  When it
started, he enjoyed it too.
I always include her when
I post the video because of course, yes.
That's why team R. Yes.  Yes.  Toos.  Well,
ma'am, until you're the one being watched
.  It's really fun to watch mommy's videos
because the [music]
videos of mommy and her voice are very
relaxing.  Hello, team R. Yes.
We were hungry again so we cooked
buldak.  Ma'am, can you eat? I ca
n't. How can you get angry at
home? How can you get angry? Is there drama in
this? No, what's wrong? [laughter]
I want to hear that, mommy. Okay, please.
How can you pretend that you're really angry
with us? It's not like I'm too angry.
She's crying too. It's a dramatic act
because it didn't mix because she was tired. Then it
seemed like she was crying.
Why are you crying now? Are you
angry because she's angry because sometimes
you can't help it. It's hot.
We were just riding our motorbikes, ma'am, when we went to the
market.  So when you get home,
I'll wash the groceries so
they don't get messy.  They won't be
confused.  Why are you angry?  There's just no reason
because sometimes there's an "Ok" (Okay).  When
I first arrive, sometimes they already chop the
garlic, onion, or
sometimes they forget.  I told
you to cut it so
I could start.  Well, that's just it
.
That's what makes you the most angry.
Yes.  That's right.
Not strong at all.
Not at all.  Of course, he won't be able to hold you
back because while
your mother and father are here,
you should love them.  Ah, that's what I always
[musically] say.  You know I saw
that on TikTok [clears throat]
it's such a privilege that you can still
call your mom and she will answer.  Because
I saw the TikToks where
their mothers died and they were like,
"Mom, this is mom, they cried."  No one will
respond.
Kiss sleeps [laughter]
' right?  That's all, what's the privilege
of having a mommy? It seems like a cool
mommy, right?  Yes.  It's too much like mommy has
values.  Yes.
I'm happy for you, mom.  Thank you,
ma'am.
Yes.  I'll just live here.  [laughter]
But you've never had a boyfriend?
Never.
Or is it true?  [laughter]
Yes, indeed.  Nothing.  Just crushes and crushes.
No one is listening to me. No one is listening.
Nothing.  Who?  What?  So there's a
little bit.  Nothing.  You don't
see anything.  visiting you?  There was no sign of him
leaving, nor did he say goodbye.
Sometimes he would leave with
his friend.  That's all.  Who is
your friend now?  My boyfriend.  Ah
[laughter] That's it.  That's it
.   They were
n't classmates, they were
his classmates before, they became his friends.
But are you planning to go to college?  Yes.
I was actually thinking about a course.
What course do you want?  Because it seems like
he really cares about what
he's ignoring.
He just doesn't like anything that just goes with him.  Okay.
He won't be as bad as
you might think at a festival [laughter]
like that.  Of course, the chefs who are
digging up
potatoes in the fields in the valley are the ones who cook mommy's food.  That's how
we are in Taytay.  That's the
menudo, that's how big the basin is.
Maybe that's not what
he'll cook.  How are you doing now that you're pregnant?
You're still cooking, but
not anymore.  You know it's nice
to be a housewife, but because you already had a life
[music] before you got married.   Just
like you, you're an actor.  I
became an actress and then it seems like you're not
the typical housewife who really loves
mommy because I think mommy is
the real housewife but
[music] since we became showbiz,
you've learned to be organized, I feel like
we're going to have a hard time.  Are
you getting it?  [music] Yes.  Because you already have friends
, you already have a life.  You got to know
yourself outside before you got
married.  You already have a world.  That's why
I admire mothers who truly
leave their old lives behind.
You, mommy, before you got married,
you were working, but
you just focused on getting pregnant.
You just focused [on music] on
your wife and your child.
What, ma'am, where did I work as a maid
?   It's
different.  There is one in monosize
.  They are not there yet.
Oh really?  Mommy,
what was your last job before you got married?  [music]
Before you get pregnant, you
still have help.  Still asleep.  Okay, go
wash my pint with the others
[laughter]. Let's just do it.
That's not really true.
Yes.  I've experienced all the
hardships.  Besides, I also want
my children to learn about household chores.
Especially the women.  Oh right.  Especially.
Yes.  So that at least even if the
maid forbids it, she can survive.  We're like, Yes.
We can.  When did you think, mom, that I had
made it?  I made it in life.   The
Lord has truly blessed me.
[music] Riza became an actress.  When
he was still young.  Yes.  I really can't
believe that this is what
we are.  The roof is high, this is
our life.  That's right.
That's why we are so thankful to the
Lord and Sait Bulaga because they are the ones who
changed our lives.  Yes.
Raiz plays an instrument [music].  Yes.
Raiza, when did you think
our life had become beautiful?  I
made it.  When I gave them a
house that was in order.  No more
debt.  I can eat three times a
day.  It's my dream, but it's
also my dream because I want [music] to
really lift my family out of hardship.
So when you were making money, you didn't make
music that was great because that was
my goal.  You know that's where I
really believe in Filipinos.  Isn't that what
Filipinos really owe?  When
you grow, your family should be with you
.  The fact is that now there is a team Riza
or you should be the one hiring
him.  [laughter] Yes, we're in reverse
now.  Yes.  But it's funny because
I see that all these years that
you've achieved and you've stayed
in the [music] industry, your corn hasn't disappeared
.  It's funny.
Let's kiss.  [laughter] Here we go again.
Kiss again.  No.  It's
really funny.  It's refreshing for
him [laughs] to be able to kiss
.  Tap when I have nothing more to say,
let's just kiss.  That's why I got pregnant.
[laughter] My husband and I couldn't do anything
earlier.  we got pregnant and that's how it is,
yeah [laughter]
so that's what's funny, you're
really a comedian, yeah it's funny
[laughter]
so much I'm not making fun of him
he's serious I'm not serious when he's off,
you're going to kiss [laughter]
thank you also because what did you do to me because I
feel like mommy is
messing with me mommy didn't reply
[music] mommy is not the one who knows how to
Instagram [laughter] we're
posting to her mommy team you know
mommy I loved you so much in
my second trimester [music] because
I had so many cravings for cooking you made me want to order
[laughter] mommy because it seems like
you enjoy cooking then she's calm because she's
calm she cooks relaxing the
video is calm or let's put
[music] like this you'll eat after you
eat alone follow
mommy then if you're not [music]
happy then bash it [laughter] so it's
copyrighted
please report please so that
the
[laughter]
Facebook says
Riza is also endless.  Riza, what about you? Do
you have a TikTok? What do you have?
I saw you dancing on TikTok, but
you're not really a vlog vlogger
or anything.  I just started vlogging.
This is my vlog
.  Delete that.  [laughter]
Paki-delete laughed.  I thought it was me
laughing
at the prank.  Okay, if you can.
[music] Just a bet.
Just bet.  Why?  Sometimes he's the one who really
works hard at creating
content.  [music]
I just thought about it.  Pretend
we're leaving like last time, ma'am, it's
her birthday [music] or we
surprised her or it was a surprise because she just
bought a car, ma'am.  Ah wow,
congratulations on buying a car.   My
sister and I are talking.  I said, "What do you think
R and May want?" What's the
call?  He said I know what
he likes about milk tea,
hey tea.
That's milk tea.  [laughter]
Baby or milk tea.  Oh, hi.  You know,
he said that's what he wanted to do, to be able
to go to Hong Kong again.  Okay,
I said, what do you want, let's book.   Let's
book.  What should we do with him?
Let's surprise.  So,
everyone spent money, Team R is proud
of what you did, what you ate,
yes.  He's the one who has it all for free
.  That's it, ma'am, and when she got
there, ate Nicole said it wasn't like it was her
birthday, ma'am, it was all about vlogging
.  [laughter]
You should return it, ma'am, it's a waste.
Because, ma'am, do you know, ma'am,
I really feel sad when I can't
upload.  Even though I'm sick and have a
fever, I'll force myself to upload.  Ah, you
should get rid of the internet
[laughter] you're going to be late because she's team
Risa, she's really good, yes now,
ma'am, I said that at least now
Mama can help because
we have something,
she's crying [laughter]
I didn't cry or you were in my hand,
sister, what's wrong, oh, that's serious, may the
Lord bless you because I didn't expect it to
help and oh, it's not
just Raya who can be blessed
[music]
you too.  Yes.  That's why, ma'am,
I am so grateful to the Lord.
He gave us so many
blessings.
[music]
So thank you so much for guesting and
for being here.  They even went to [music] for
me because I actually really wanted to go
camping with mommy.  That's why
the doctor talked to me [music] and said
I need to go to
bed first.  I wondered if the
three of us could just sleep in the room.  [laughter] There's
nothing, I said nothing.
Yes.  My wife has no place
[laughter].  Yes.  But it's better,
ma'am, here at your house.  We even arrived
at your house, which is so beautiful it looks like a
palace.  Mommy is so big
.  Too big.  It's only now that it's
coming to these things.  It's too
big, ma'am.  Oh, so many sofas.  How
beautiful.  What will we do later?  Let's head to
Jerusalem.  [laughter]
Even my sofa was torn apart,
you're going to take the sofas apart one by one.
[laughter]
When are you going to invite me to your house?
Well, nothing yet, ma'am.  Besides, it's a bit
dusty, so it's not allowed to go upstairs.  It seems like it's
all discouragement.  [laughter]
He really doesn't want to invite you.  That's all
.  It seems like nothing.  Oh, you're not allowed
there.  There's a lot of [laughter] dust all over the
negatives.  Since when have you been
my doctor?
Thank you very much.  I wish that all
your dreams come true.  come true
[music] in Jesus name.  And I wish that
whoever becomes
your first boyfriend will love you so much that
you will find a man who will truly
value you and treasure you and
love you the way your
mommy loves you and of course you should love
your family [music] and respect your family.
Thank you so much for inviting me.   It's
delicious.  Is that okay?  Oh, that's
delicious.
Delicious.  Hooray!  But it wasn't
recorded.  So let's repeat this [laughter],
okay?  You will buy something
like that again.  You are a loser.  You're at a loss.  There is a
galunggong there.
That's possible.  That's okay too.  There you go.  Hey,
someone wants to say hello to you.  Just wait, just
wait.  I'm alive.  Oh, just wait.  Don't
turn off that beam for now.  Mute it
first.  Meet first.  Someone will say hello
first.  Hello.  [whispering]
Me.  Beam knows me.  I thought it was fake
news.  Can you say hi to my vlog beam?
Just say hi.
Oh you're on live now.  Hello.  Not live.
Just a vlog.  Tell them that you know me.
He doesn't want to believe it.  Well, we met
you, Aunt Alex.
Okay.  Aunt Alex, you are the coolest
aunt I ever had.  Auntie, you don't
visit me anymore.  That's right.  Because of course
I'm just surprised you're already here in
Itulaga.  I said that
Ano had already returned home.  No.  I didn't know.  I thought
you're in the statsaka I thought because
your mom also is maybe later just sensitive to
me.  That's annoying.   Let's
get it over with, bro.  You should
go to the cond.  Okay, Bims,
you're the one who's going to pull out the
umbilical cord of my baby [laughter],
you're going to be so upset, huh?
[laughter]
But Aunt Alex, you haven't aged.
Just because your friends are old, does that make you look older
?  As long as Pimp's friends don't seem to be
getting older.  It was their first time
eating crab.  King crab.
Crab.  Yes.  That's how big it is.  It's their first time
.  So the second time you should be
together.  Yes.  My legs are intact.
See you soon.
Okay.  Bye-bye.  Love you.
See you soon.  See you soon.  Okay.
Bye.  Bye-bye.  I saw the thank you,
babe.  [laughter]
Mommy's not here.  Mommy, baby.  The one who calls
the big one is the one who calls the little one.  Did
you see it?  Thanks H. Thanks babe.
[laughter] Not really
.  They didn't call.  Just kidding.
[music]
ه